Jeyson Guzman

Front End Developer

Bogotá, Colombia (zona horaria) (+57) 3238082776 <u>ievsonkmguzman@gmail.com</u> https://www.linkedin.com/in/jeyson-guzman/ https://jeyson-guzman.vercel.app/

Frontend Developer with over 2 years of experience in JavaScript frameworks and macro frameworks, specializing in React JS, Next JS, and Angular. My focus is centered on code quality and a continuous commitment to learning. I am an expert in implementing efficient and optimized code architectures, achieving success rates of 60% to 70% according to specific requirements, utilizing monorepo approaches for smoother management. I possess a deep understanding of agile methodologies, particularly **SCRUM**, enabling timely and effective deliveries

EXPERIENCE

Supremacy Kingdom, Team Leader — march, 2023 - august, 2023

Team Leader — april, 2023 - august, 2023

- Optimize code and provide a higher-quality code structure for the frontend
- Success achieved with the team in completing the project, resulting in satisfaction

Front End developer — march, 2023 - april, 2023

- Completion of the web page to 100%
- API queries implementation and optimization

Tech Stack: Angular, Next.JS,git,Azure, Azure DevOps, Api Rest

Devsavant, Front end developer — january, 2022 - january, 2023

- Developing a plugin for Microsoft Teams and webinars.
- Development of an administrative dashboard
- Implementation of design for various projects.

Tech Stack: React JS, Node JS, git, AWS, Angular

Globant, Trainee

Data Scientist — july, 2021 - october, 2021

Analysis of data from the database.

Tech Stack: Python, MySQL, MongoDB, PostgresDB, pyShark, git

Front End developer — november, 2021 - january, 2022

Learning and implementing knowledge in React JS web pages

Tech Stack: React, git

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Advanced: Javascript, Typescript, Api Rest; Intermediate: python, nodeJS; Basic: Flutter

Frameworks Tools: Advanced: ReactJS, Next JS; Intermediate: Angular; Basic: Flask, React Native

Data Base: MySQL, MongoDB, PostgresDB

Tools: Git, Github, Jira, Slack, Firebase, AWS, GPC, Azure DevOps, Visual Studio Code

Agile: SCRUM

Languages: Intermediate: English; Native: Spanish.

EDUCATION

Sena – Ibague, Colombia Análisis y desarrollo de sistemas de información 2022

CERTIFICATIONS

Next.js: El framework de React para producción — Udemy. 2023

Fundamentos de typescript - Platzi. 2022

Front End Developer - Platzi. 2022.

React (react hooks) - udemy. 2021.

Profesional de python - Platzi. 2021